["Like Sugar" by Chaka Khan playing]
♪ Why, with the state that I'm in ♪
♪ Everybody here is dancing ♪
♪ All I wanna do is get ya ♪
[man]
Mila and I work at Valentino together.
Mila's style is intergalactic.
[man]
She hasn't done a whole lot of dating.
As soon as she meets someone,
they jump straight into that relationship.
♪ Why, with the state that I'm in ♪
♪ Everybody here is dancing ♪
♪ All I wanna do is get ya ♪
♪ Body next to mine, yeah ♪
♪ Baby, won't you stand up to me? ♪
♪ Come around and make a move ♪
[woman] Mila does not date a lot, no.
But she wants that, you know,
two point five kids, picket fence.
She wants a family.
♪ It's like ♪
♪ I like it ♪
♪ Like sugar ♪
♪ It's like sugar ♪
Hello. How are you?
-Hi.
-Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
-I'm Mila.
-Mila, Nina.
Nice to meet you.
How're you feeling?
-I'm good.
-You're good?
I'm a little nervous, but, like...
I've never been on a blind date before.
Me either.
-This is all very new.
-I know.
-And I don't know you, so that's a plus.
-Yeah, it's like...
"What's going on?" I didn't know
what I was gonna expect. You're gorgeous.
-Thank you. You too.
-Thank you.
-I love your outfit.
-[Nina] You hungry?
-Yeah, I am.
[Nina] So, you want to go eat?
-Yeah.
-Let's do it.
-[Mila] I'm excited about tonight.
-Yeah.
-It's fun.
-Hi.
-Hi. How are you?
-Good. How are you?
-I'm good. Nice to--
Be careful.
-What's your name?
-I'm Mila.
-That's a pretty name.
-Yes.
-I'm Jarry.
-I love your accent.
-Thank you. It's a weird accent.
-No. Where are you from?
I grew up in Wales and England,
-and then also Connecticut, so it's like--
-So it's like a mix of all things?
-It's a mess that no one recognizes.
-Okay.
-What about you?
-I was born in Illinois,
and, like, I lived there,
California for a little bit,
and I lived in Michigan for four years,
and then I've been here.
-You've been all over.
-A little bit.
-I'm so bad with geography.
-With geography?
-I had a crush on my fourth-grade teacher.
-Oh.
Which is when I feel like
we learned about geography.
-I don't remember much.
-You were busy looking at him?
-Her.
-Oh, her?
-Yeah. [laughs]
-Sorry!
[laughs] I'll never forget her.
-Uh-huh.
-Yeah. [laughs]
I'm really digging the whole vibe here.
I like your style.
-Thank you.
-It's pretty cool.
-I like yours, too.
-Thanks.
-How long has your hair been that color?
-A month.
-Is it Manic Panic, the color?
-Girl, no. I have no fucking clue.
-Who did it?
-I did it myself.
-Oh, okay.
-Yeah.
I have what I... [laughs]
-What I describe as Kunta Kinte hair.
-No.
I'm not gonna let that rock, no.
I-I-- But I love my hair now. I love it.
-It's awesome. It's nice and thick.
-It's dope. It's amazing. Yes.
-What are you drinking?
-A Stella Artois.
I'm gonna have a Jameson and Coke.
I'm a little nervous. I got to, like...
-calm the nerves a little bit.
-Okay. Yeah, it's totally fine.
-No judgement.
-I'm not judging you.
I don't go on a lot of dates.
-Me either.
-[woman] What would you like?
She would like a Stella, please,
and I would love a Jameson and Coke.
-[woman] Okay.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
What do you identify yourself as
in terms of, like, femme, stud, stem...
-I love that you know all the terms..
-...tomboy, androgynous?
I'd say I'm like a stud.
I embrace my femininity,
but I present very masculine.
-Gotcha.
-It makes me feel more confident.
Like, if I'm too girlie,
I feel, like, awkward.
-Well, I'm actually bi. Yeah.
-Okay.
What was your moment,
and you, like, knew you were bisexual?
It was never really a defining moment.
-It kind of felt like my essence, I guess.
-The way you felt. Right.
I'm more of like an AG, or a soft AG.
-What's an AG?
-Aggressive.
More, you know, the dominant one.
-You understand what I mean?
-I got you. No, I do.
-'Cause aggressives can be--
-Right.
-Exactly.
-That's the spectrum. That's all the way--
-The left and the right.
-Yeah.
That's the polar opposite of
a lipstick lesbian or something like that.
So what do you consider yourself?
-I would just say like a femme.
-Okay.
Sometimes I won't be
in a full thing of makeup,
but I won't come out the house
looking crazy.
But, see, I like that.
I like when, like, feminine women
throw on like a pair of sweatpants
and just make that shit look sexy.
Yeah.
So, what do you do? What are you into?
-I do, like, editorial makeup.
-Oh, cool.
For, like, photo shoots
and things like that.
-That's amazing.
-Magazines. Yeah, it's fun.
My work was just in Vogue Italy
for the third time.
-So I was really happy about that.
-Congratulations!
Thank you.
So we're celebrating. Wait, cheers to you.
-We're celebrating.
-Wait, that just happened?
Yeah, like, three days ago.
And then I work at Valentino,
like a sales associate.
Oh, that's amazing.
They have, like, amazing-- Oh, my God.
-I'm jealous!
-Clothing.
-Yes.
Do you get free stuff?
Not free. It--
Do you get like a friends and family
discount code?
-What do you do?
-I'm in sales.
-I work in the fashion industry.
-What do you do?
I have my own brand, so, yeah.
How long have you had your own--
What is it, a fashion line?
-Five or six years now. Yeah, so--
-Wow, that's awesome.
I love acting,
and modeling pays the bills.
-Okay.
-I enjoy modeling, you know?
Okay, yeah.
You know, acting makes me feel alive.
And modeling makes me feel
like I look bored in jeans.
-That is my job, to look bored in jeans.
-You said, "Look bored in jeans."
[laughs]
I've always been
into fitness and wellness.
I ran track for Jamaica when I was 16.
I competed in the CARIFTA Games,
got a gold medal there,
and, then, shortly after that,
-got my scholarship and I moved to the US.
-Okay.
-And now I am a fitness manager.
For 15 years,  I've been in nightlife.
I used to throw the largest queer party
here in New York.
People think like, "Oh, you throw parties.
You must be, like, a fuckboy
-or, like, a party animal."
-Yeah. Are you a fuckboy?
No. It's an aesthetic.
It's not a personality trait.
It's just how I dress.
-This is just my nature.
-Just a question. Making sure.
-Well, I get that a lot.
-Okay.
My favorite is when I'm at the bar,
and a guy will be like,
"Are you into girls?" I'm like, "Yeah."
They'll be like,
"So you guys, like, scissor?"
And I'm like,
"It's more like this, but, yes."
-Yes, we do.
-Sometimes. It's not our go-to move.
Lesbians have a bajillion ways to get off.
-Honestly.
-If you knew,
maybe you'd be pleasing your girl
a little bit more.
Right?
-Hello, ladies. Your table is ready.
-Hi.
-Okay, perfect.
-Thank you.
Okay. Perfect.
There you go. Let me know
if you need anything.
-Great, thank you very much.
-No problem.
So, have you dated much
since you've been in New York?
No. All my dates have turned into,
like, long-term relationships.
Oh, so not much of a dater,
more of a monogamist.
I am...
-Yeah.
-That's the lesbian way, right?
-I guess.
-Isn't that what they say?
-I'm not into stereotypes, but...
-Thank you.
That's what they say, but I didn't know
that was the way. I was just like,
"These women keep finding me,
and then I'm in relationships."
If you find a good one,
you gotta lock it down.
-Never know when you'll find another.
-That's the truth.
I've definitely heard that dating
in the lesbian community is super small.
-You found it, you're always--
-It's really small.
-Yeah.
-You'll go to a bar
and you'll be with five of your exes,
and it's just, like, normal.
Or, like, your ex becomes your best friend
-and you're all hanging out together.
-My God!
All of the lesbians
hang out in the same spots.
-Okay.
-There's, like, Cubbyhole.
-Do you know, like, Hot Rabbit?
-Yeah.
And then there's Henrietta Hudson,
Monster, and Stonewall.
Now, like the new thing is, like,
you and all of your friends
go to a straight bar
and you make that bar gay.
How does that work?
Word of mouth. You're new to the scene.
You'll get thrown
to the wolves eventually.
You said, "Thrown to the wolves"?
Oh, yeah. It's like a lion's den there.
Yeah.
I find the New York dating scene
to be a little messy.
I keep hearing these things.
-It is.
-Uh-huh.
Because I'm starting to appreciate
a more...
seasoned woman,
and a seasoned doesn't necessarily mean
that she's older.
-She's seasoned in who she is.
-Yeah.
And these girls don't strike me
as seasoned, so why waste my time?
Game-players. They're playing games.
Lots of people will say, "Oh, I wouldn't
want to date someone who's bisexual.
That means they want
to sleep with everyone."
-Yeah.
-I'm like, "That's not true."
What do you say when people
come to you, and it's like,
"I don't believe in bisexual"?
I think I would probably just say
that they're ignorant...
-Yeah.
-and they don't actually understand
that there's an entire spectrum
of human desire.
And it's also just not, I don't know,
not my problem
-that they don't see it that way.
-Yeah.
I know for me, its--
like, getting hit on by a lot of guys,
and I thought the way to stop that
was like,
"I'm gay," or, "I'm a lesbian."
Do they say, like,
-"But I can change your mind"?
-Exactly.
-"You haven't seen my dick."
"I can change your mind.
We can have a threesome."
I think especially in New York,
you get so much of that energy.
And who is to say that
this is what a lesbian should look like,
or a straight person should look like?
-I think that's ridiculous.
-Yeah.
I usually date girls
that pretty much look like me.
That sounds really egotistical...
-No.
-like I'm about myself.
But...
-Blonde or brunette.
-Mm-hmm.
[chuckles]
My first girlfriend found me on Instagram
and, like, slid in my DMs.
[sighs wearily]
-The same for you?
-Oh, God.
Sliding in DMs is, like,
the new dating app.
-Yeah. No, it is.
-My first girlfriend, though,
was ten years ago and I tweeted her.
Oh, my God.
But then ever since then, it's been, like,
either I'm dating my ex's ex,
or I'm dating girls who, like, DM me.
Have you ever dated a black girl?
-No.
-No? Okay.
Have you ever dated a white girl?
-Yes. My last--
-Oh, damn. [laughs]
So, what were your exes like?
Do you have a type?
-More like stud, androgynous.
-So, like, handsome like me,
-tall like me?
-Beautiful like you.
-Oh, thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Or are you just dishing compliments?
-[laughs]
-I really like your earrings.
-Thank you.
-Did I say that already?
-I have piercings.
-Yeah, I like it.
-Yeah.
-Do you have any tattoos?
-I do.
-Good tattoos are hot, right?
-Yes.
I have...
I think, like, seven. I want to say seven.
-Maybe seven.
-Okay.
I love tattoos in the sense
that it's a permanent piece of art.
You know, I look at the body
as, like, a canvas.
You know, I'm not attached to my body.
-Your soul is in this vessel.
-Right.
You know, but it's just that's what it is.
It's just a vessel. You know what I mean?
So I want it to be a way
that I can express myself
and, you know, express who I am.
-This one is actually my most recent one.
-Mm-hmm.
I'm a Gemini.
Geminis are ruled by Mercury,
the planet Mercury, so--
-Yes. Know your houses.
-Yes. [laughs]
-Yes. Okay.
-Yeah.
So this is the sign for Mercury,
-like, the symbol.
-That's dope.
Yeah.
[giggles]
I have, like, this quote
on the back of my neck.
Do you see it?
Yes, I see it. It's, like, Arabic?
-It's Hindu.
-Hindu?
Yeah. It's a Hindu monk mantra...
Um...
And it says, "Om gam ganapataye namaha."
-Which means?
-It means
fighting off negativity,
like, warding off negativity
and any, um, obstacles and roadblocks
in your future.
Can you say that?
Om gam... wait.
[laughs]
Om gam...
Wait. [laughs]
-Om...
-[laughs]
Om gam...
Can you say it?
-No. [laughs]
-Okay.
Gan... Ganapataye.
There's no way--
There's no way I can say all of this.
...gam gan...
Om gam...
ganapataye.
Namaha!
I feel like I'm, like, throwing tomahawks,
like, "Namahawk!"
I feel like I'm saying
some weird cult shit right now.
Just like, whats--
You're not a joining a cult.
You're not signing your life away.
[both] Om gam ganapataye namaha.
-Yeah.
-Okay. Yeah.
[Mila] Pretty fascinating.
Do you have any tattoos?
-Not one. Zero tattoo. Blank slate.
-Really?
-Nothing.
-Wow. That's crazy.
-Clean as a whistle.
-Okay.
I hooked up with a girl who was like,
"You have no tattoos?"
I'm like, "Is that a deal breaker?"
Like, "Oops. I'm sorry." Like...
How was you with coming out
with your, like, family?
-My family?
-Yeah.
You know, I came out because I went to see
Hair at my college
and there was a nude scene
and there was this one girl in it
and I was just drawn to her.
And I had a boyfriend at the time.
And I ended up cr--
Like, my blonde...  I was blonde,
high femme. I was a go-go dancer.
-And like-- I was straight girl, like--
-Okay. You got a past.
It was crazy, yeah. So, um...
I went to the cast party
and she put her arm around me.
"Do you like boys or girls?"
I was like, "I'm not gay."
Like freaked out and left,
and then messaged her.
I was like, "You're the first girl
I've seen and thought dirty things about.
Like, I don't what to do."
Broke up with my boyfriend,
went to a party with her...
told my best friend,
and then called my mom and was like...
"I met this girl.
Like, just, you know, call me back.
I'm dating a girl." And, like, hung up.
[laughs]
-But she was super--
-Cool and understanding about it?
Yeah. I was really lucky.
Really, really lucky.
I was raised on a big family,
so coming out... that was rough.
But my dad,
he's a part of a men's ministry...
-Oh, God.
-in Texas.
He was like, "It doesn't matter
what I think or anyone else thinks."
He's like, "As long as you're happy,
you have to live your life."
And I was real happy.
-Yes! Daddy, come through.
-It's like, "Thank you for loving me."
-I like him already.
-Yeah. He's really dope.
-Oh, my goodness. I'm so happy for you.
-Yeah.
-I've had a really great night.
-This was actually really great.
Better than you thought?
-Yeah.
-Yes.
Yeah, like, I honestly didn't know
what to expect.
"Who is about to come around the block?
Who am I about to--
Who is--"
-No, it was definitely nerve-racking.
-Yeah.
Do you want to maybe take a walk?
-Yeah, let's go.
-Okay.
Let's go.
-[Nina] Enjoy yourself?
-I did. I didn't know what to expect.
Honestly, I really kind of
had low expectations.
Okay.
I don't like giving myself
high expectations. 'Cause then I feel--
-You don't wanna be disappointed.
-Exactly, you know?
So, how do you think, like,
this date would be different if...
I were, like, a man?
Hmm.
I usually find that
-men I date are more aggressive...
-Okay.
and, then, women,
usually a bit more reserved.
[Christina] I want somebody
who knows what she wants...
and who's willing to...
-build with me.
-Yeah.
And somebody who understands that
she doesn't have to have it all together.
-Like, we can do it all together.
-Yeah.
-[man] Hey, how are we tonight?
-[Mila] Good. How are you?
[man] I'm all right. Thank you for asking.
Can I help you with anything?
Can I get the strawberry?
-[man] Strawberry. All right.
-And a scoop of the Dark Matter.
-[man] A scoop of the Dark Matter. Got it.
-Yes. Thank you.
I want to try
the vegan strawberry jam cookie, please?
-We'll share one.
-[man] Share that one?
Yeah, that's fine.
Dark Matter-- I have to try that.
I don't even know what it--
-It just sounds cool.
-But it's just... Okay.
-"Dark Matter."
-It does sound really good.
[man] I got one single scoop for two.
Thank you.
-That looks good.
-You wanna taste it?
-It's so good. It's my favorite.
-Yeah?
-Thank you.
-[man] You're welcome.
[Nina] Oh, that looks good.
-[man] Vegan in the cone.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Are you jealous of my cone?
Oh, yeah. I do want a lick.
-You got to share with me, too.
-Yeah. Taste it.
-That's good, no?
-I don't hate it.
You don't hate it?
I don't hate it at all.
Should I try this one?
You want to try first?
-You hated it.
-I don't hate it.
-You don't have to lie to me.
-I'm not a fan of chocolate ice cream.
I like chocolate everything.
And don't make any comments.
I'm not cliché like that.
I wasn't about to...
I didn't say anything.
-I don't need to hear that nonsense.
-I didn't say anything. [laughs]
-Should we get out of here?
-Let's go.
Let me make sure you don't get wet.
-Not yet, anyway.
-Thank you.
-[laughs] I'm gonna beat your ass.
-Stop threatening me.
-We're on a date.
-I'm so...
[Mila laughs] You're ridiculous.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
[Charlotte] As long as you're laughing,
we're having a good time.
[Ashley] It was really nice
getting to know you.
You as well. Like, I really...
I gained a lot of insight
about just like, you know,
something you've had, like,
more experience and time in.
You do know now
that, like, you're stuck with me forever.
-That's fine. I'm okay with that.
-All right, how about this?
-Pride's next week.
-Yes.
I'm having a bunch of my girlfriends
come over to pregame.
Okay.
Why don't you come over, then we'll go
to Stonewall and have drinks there?
That's right were I live,
-so it's really hard--
-I've never been in Stonewall.
-Are you kidding me?
-No, I haven't.
-I've heard about it. It's a monumental--
-Jesus Christ. You're not even a lesbian.
I am! I've been through enough! I am.
[Christina]
What did you think of the date?
I think it was...
What did you think of it?
No! You can't answer my question
with a question.
I think it was nice.
I enjoyed getting to know you as a person.
As opposed to what, if not a person?
No! Like, actually getting to know--
'Cause, you know, sometimes
things like this are just bullshit.
It's so surface, and it's not in-depth.
You know what I'm saying?
I think that's a waste of time. Like,
meet somebody, put it all on the table.
Okay, we're on the same page.
I just appreciate your energy,
your conversation.
-[Mila] Of course.
-Yeah.
I feel like it's so rare to find someone
that's at least on the same, like...
-plane as you. You know what I mean?
-Yes.
So to be able to, like, sit down
and have a conversation with you
to where you, like,
actually understand what I'm saying,
like, I really appreciate that.
So... Yeah.
Yes, of course!
-We definitely got to stay in touch.
-Yeah, we do. Yes.
-Let's exchange numbers, 'cause...
-Yeah.
You know, I definitely want to...
-see you again.
-Okay. Me too.
So, you're not, like, 1,000% my type.
You know, I do go
for more, like, androgynous women.
But, I mean, I did really enjoy
all of the conversations we had
and just, like, really getting to know you
just, like, as a person.
I feel like, yeah, it was really nice
to get to know you.
Um, and I'm actually glad to, like,
see someone outside of my type.
-I think you'll get stuck in a rut.
-Yes. [laughs]
-Being in, like, that bubble.
-Yeah.
So, when do we do this again?
I was gonna be like,
"Are we doing this again?"
-I don't like asking that question.
-Why?
Because then it's like, "Oh, yes or no."
No, I want you to know were I am at.
When do we do this again?
I would definitely maybe,
like, hang out...
-Okay.
-instead of like an actual date.
-I should get your number.
-Yeah, no. You can.
-I can?
-Yeah.
-I'm gonna whip my phone out now.
-[laughs]
If I text you, are you gonna text me back?
-Nope.
-Wow.
I'm gonna hand you that,
so you can just put all of the info in
and I don't mess it up.
-It better not be a fake number.
-It's gonna be a fake number, too.
[laughs]
I will be talking to you soon.
I'll slide in your DM later. Bye.
-Bye, love.
-It was so nice meeting you.
-Have a great night.
-You too.
How do I get out of here?
[laughing] It's this.
Oh, wow. Thank you.
-See? I need to keep you around.
-[laughs]
-Bye, love.
-Bye.
-This was an amazing date.
-Good.
[Charlotte] Um...
-If I kiss you, are you gonna be mad?
-No.
Oh, you're a good kisser, too?
Oh, we should definitely do this again.
[giggles]
All right! Yes, it was awesome.
Thank you so much.
[both laugh]
We'll have to do something soon.
All right. Cool.
-So, you got my number? Hit me up.
-Yes. Definitely.
All right. Have a good night.
-You too, boo.
-Thank you.
["Youth" (Gryffin remix)
by Troye Sivan playing]
♪ My youth, my youth is yours ♪
♪ Trippin' on skies, sippin' waterfalls ♪
♪ Runaway now and forevermore ♪
♪ My youth, my youth is yours ♪
♪ A truth so loud you can't ignore ♪
♪ My youth, my youth ♪
♪ My youth ♪
♪ My youth is yours ♪
[Charlotte] Well, hey.
Hi.
That was like slow motion. I loved it.
You gave me a slow-motion romantic kiss,
so New York City.
-I hate you... so much.
-How are you?
-I'm good.
-You going purple again?
-Like lavender.
-Lavender's good on you.
Yeah. Thank you.
You look super cute.
-You look super cute.
-Stop.
-You always flirt with me.
-Whatever.
Should we get out of here,
second-date style?
-I'm done with you.
-I'm not done with you. Let's go.
[Charlotte] Maybe we can find some place
we've both never been.
-Would you be down for that?
-Yeah. I love a good adventure.
♪ My youth is yours ♪